CHAHANA TYAGI

(Software Engineer)

88020 23335 tyagichahana.github.io linkedin.com/in/chahana-tyagi chahanatyagi16@gmail.com New Delhi

Profile

Front-end Developer with 2.8 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing web app. Self-Organized, disciplined, quality-oriented, love to work with the fast growing technologies some of those are: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS,Redux and it's middleware etc.

Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TOKOPEDIA (2019- PRESENT)

Working on Campaign Management Project which is a Internet marketing platform to run all type of campaigns. I have developed this project from scratch using technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, Redux-Saga.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, PAYTM PAYMENT BANK

Working on front-end technologies for banking Platform, some of these React, Redux, HTML, CSS.

UI DEVELOPER, AGILE APT SOLUTIONS - 2016-2018

Worked on various projects using following technologies: HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS.

Projects

CAMPAIGN MANAGEMENT - TOKOPEDIA

- It's a marketing platform to run all type of campaigns like Push notification, SMS, Email and InApp. User can check the reports of all Campaigns on its dashboard which is developed using HighCharts for analysis.
- Technologies used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, HighChart.
- Implemented the redux saga with redux and react and use generator and yield concept.

BO PANEL - PAYTM PAYMENTS BANK

- Implemented the redux saga with redux and react and use generator and yield concept.
- Implemented unit testing on components.

STUDENT AID - BUY AND SELL BOOKS

eCommerce platform for books

TOUREE- SINGAPORE TOURISM BOARD

- It's a panel used by hotel admin to know all the requests raised by their guests by using mobile app of the hotel.
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, ReactJs, HighChart, Redux.

PINDDY- BUY AND SELL CROPS BY FARMERS

- It's a platform where farmers can sell their crops and people can buy from them.
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, ReactJs, Redux.

Education

Delhi University – B.Tech, 2013-2017 **C.B.S.E** – A.I.S.S.E, 2011-2012 **H.B.S.E** – A.I.S.S.C.E, 2009-2010

Skills

Scripting – ReactJS, Redux, Redux Middleware, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, SPA, Unit Testing

Package Manager – NPM, Yarn Version Control – GIT